(MUSIC) vonita :3
Oh wow! I didn't see you there :v How are you? (RIP door)
Aahh! What the fuck?
Hello, Little Creatures of the Lord! How are you? We're here...
With a snow mallet! (A lot of snow)
(moans)
¡¡AAAHH!!
Well, here I am still on vacation, okay? Eh, like I said live and all that stuff.
Eehh, I was going to go on vacation, with the family and all the fishing, okay?
What..., I mean... behind this video making machine...
There's also a human being, you know?...
There is also a human being...
With feelings and stuff...
OH WELL!!
We're here in the middle of a... a town, right? Far from the edge of God, in the middle of a mountain called...
Wengen
Wen Wenen... :v
It's a small town in Switzerland, right?... Eehh
And as you can see, it's covered in snow, I mean. This is awesome, it's like a dream come true.
I haven't seen this much snow in a long time, man.
¡Wii :D!
I've been waiting to do this for a long time...
So let's go
¡¡OOH!!
This is life :D
Fuck, fuck, fuck!! (Shit, shit, shit)
♫ It's frozen! ♫
♫ It's gotten into me everywhere ♫ 7u7
♫ I'M RETARDED ♫ :U
♫ SHIT SHIT ♫ D:
♫ SHIT SHIT SHIT ♫
¡¡NO NO NO NO NO!! D:
It's gotten into my other one now!
¡¡aaAAaah!!
We don't have to make too much noise, okay? Because this house
It belongs to a lady... who rented it to us
Like, he's going to think we're fucking crazy, sick in the head.
And we are! Okay?! (It's true :V) But... We don't want to give that image!
But anyway, before continuing I wanted to wish you, okay?...
Happy holidays, a happy new year *kiss*
And all those cute and kawaii things, okay? (damn, you're late }:v)
Because then there are people angry with me,
Angry because I haven't said anything in any video, like congratulations or anything and... You're going to fall!
¡¡AAAHH!! (RIP iriva :v)
(laughs)
-My cell phone! -I warned you!
I mean! We came here, really, to snowboard and all that, but...
There's a little thing down here...
Wait, is there light?
What's wrong with him?
There :v
OK.
Well, as you can see, here we leave all the tables and stuff like that.
Here's mine, beautiful.
I'm not going to throw away my neighbor's.
¡¡¡YYYY!!!
There are like 800 sleds here, I mean...
I don't know who they belong to but :v (thief point :v)
I don't think they'd mind if we took one, would they? For a second or so...
Do it for the views
Do it for the subs (Por los subs)
Do it for the vine
Sir, if you're seeing this, I'm so sorry but, but...
Ajam! I'll give it back to you, okay? In one piece, HU!
I've never ridden a sled like that, man. This has got to be awesome!
Run, run! He's looking at us through the window!
Run, run!
Bottle ( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)
Aah! It just fell right on the mark!
Shit!
Run, run, run!! :v
Run, run, run!!
NO, DON'T RUN!
There's ice sledgehammer in here, man.
(laughs) There's ice hammer
-¡Rubiuh! D:
(laughs)
This must be my first time riding a wooden sled, so...
RIP Rubius :D
Happy New Year :3
Go fuck yourself. :V
I shit on the bitch!
¡¡¡¡OOoohh!!!!
¡¡¡¡OOOOOHH!!!! ¡¡AAHH!!
¡¡AAHA!!
OH Shit! No, no, no! (almost died :V)
(laughs)
Shit, man
I think the neighbor is there, watching us! D:
¡Ajam! Behave well :v
Fuck!
Let's leave this here! Let's leave this here!
And we're going to take a walk in the mountains.
(Landscape background music)
One moment...
This...
...I think it's to put it in your ass 7u7 and go down...
...full speed down a hill. :V
(Epic Music)
Mmmm...
Swiss children... ( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)
They're probably filled with Swiss chocolate. 7u7
(Moans with pleasure)
-We've talked about this before. >:l
Let me give them a little bite :(
-No way! >:(
On the arm?
-¡No!
A little bit :D
¡Hi!
(they speak in German)
¿No?
I bet I'll take a bite! (They laugh)
I'll take a bite...
He told me I can't use this but it will be!
Stupid Swiss kids stuffed with chocolate! }:v
Well, nothing!
If they don't want to play with me, I don't want to play with them either. >:v
I'm going to throw myself over here! >:D
With this! Let's see how it works. :v
Dos, ¡Ah fuck!
(epic music) ¡Unooo....!
(epic music)
(epic music) ¡C*ño! ¡Locoooo!
(laughs like crazy)
(epic music)
*Wii Sports Music*
I've covered my face in snow.
Can you see?
-Yes... (laughter)
¡Ostia!
¡Uuuuuh!
Okay! Let's try the same thing, but...
...in first person.
So you can see how all the f*cking snow hits me in the face!
(epic music)
Come on
Damn, he's leaving now!
HE'S LEAVING NOW!
OK
Oh, eh!
LOOK LIKE!!
SHIT, SHIT!!
I'M TURN AROUND!!! I'M TURN AROUND!!!
NO NO NO!!
(laughs)
HAPPY NEW YEAR
This dog's balls must be freezing off. :v
Well now we're going to...
...one of the highest mountains in all of Europe...
...and we're going to take this train to Hogwarts, okay?
Run, run, it's closing!
Run run run!!
I am loving it!
-Are you sure he's leaving? We haven't looked.
If I go down, I'll die laughing.
Is this going up?
Well, as we climb this mountain...
...Eeeehh... I wanted to tell you, is that okay?
Because I haven't uploaded a video for like 2 weeks.
And it has been quite good for me, to be honest.
For my mental health (laughs)...
...Basically.
I've gone on vacation, really...
I mean, I think this is the first time I've ever done this, okay?
Going on vacation without preparing any videos or anything like that.
And my God, wait, look how beautiful this is.
For God's sake!
(Background music)
And that's it. I haven't logged into Twitter, Instagram, or YouTube...
...or anything at all, I mean. It's been like...
...TOTAL DISCONNECTION!
And well, this Christmas...
...whoa.. Eehh...
I did the typical Christmas thing, which is watch...
"Home Alone"
"Home Alone 2"
"Harry Potter"
Eeeehh...
...play a lot of Switch.
Being with family, eating a lot of food, I mean.
If you see me a little fat, that's why, okay? (laughs)
FUCK!!
My camera battery is running out and I haven't brought a spare...
...and we're about to get on the fucking... fuck!!
Okay, so yesterday...
...my camera ran out of battery.
Very well, Rubius.
I mean, always a planner and stuff like that...
But hey, I want to show you this because it's awesome, okay?
These are the most beautiful views I've ever seen in my entire fucking life,
and I'm not saying this, like, exaggerating, I mean...
It's real!
I mean, look at this, for God's sake!
F-uck, bro!
Oh my goodness, oh my goodness!
And look at all this fresh snow, man, it's like mmmm...
...makes you want to suck it, man.
(moans)
-Oh oh! Moron alert!
-Alert for retard!
Okay, so let's test the drone. I haven't used it much, okay? So...
...I don't know how this is going to turn out, but let's hope it goes well.
Let's try to get a great plan...
...Like a movie!
Well, in 3...2...1!
You should get up... aa ...
(drone sound)
¡Vale, vale! ¡Guay, guay, guay, guay!
It works!
Use the force!
(drone sound)
¡UUUuuhh!
Now the typical shot where the drone goes up and I'm down below, okay?
Come on! Let's see if it works out.
(Background music)
(drone sound) (Background music)
(laughs)
Okay, in this country they are experts in their sausages, I mean...
They have sausages everywhere,
and I ordered a MEGA ULTRA sausage here with...
...a drink, in a strange way, that is kind of typical here.
They mix alcohol, coffee... and everything is warm.
And cream.
I don't know.
It's...
It's a little strange, to be honest.
Let's see, the sausage.
It's cute, huh!
Ten out of ten!
(Saturn Barz - Gorillaz)
(Music from Wii Sports)
Can someone explain to me what this is?
I mean, why is there a child... who appears to be dead in that stroller? (laughs)
On that sleigh.
(music in the distance)
It's stiff, huh!
It's stiff, I mean. I think this one has to be
The boy is on his last legs. (laughs)
It's on its last legs. (laughs)
And they leave him lying there!
And they leave him stranded!
What's wrong with them in this country?! (laughs)
Chupa ( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°) (Only to reach 10 minutes)